

Frontend Developer Ha Noi, Vietnam

giahung197bg@gmail.com









About

Hi, my name is Hung, i'm 26 years old. I got a bachelor of Electronics Telecommunication Engineering at Ha Noi University of Science and Technology. Besides, i am really passionate about Javascript and Web Development.

I am also an open-source enthusiast and maintainer. I love how collaboration and knowledge sharing happens through open-source and I am happy to see what I do could eventually feedback to the community and industry.

Work Experience

AgileTech Vietnam Frontend Developer

Dec 2020 - Present | Nhân Hòa, quận Thanh Xuân, Hà Nội

- Worked on developing and maintaining the projects of the company.
- Training new members of the company.

Beau Agency Vietnam Frontend Developer Intern

Dec 2019 - Dec 2020 | Hoàng Văn Thái, Thanh Xuân, Hà Nội

- Worked on developing and maintaining the company's e-commerce, landing page website
- Developed and maintained the project on shopify platform.

Projects

Sách điện tử 7

Management book and national newspaper

Pinex 7

Finance social network

Maby [↗]

Book an appointment, Search for the nearest salon, Search for a salon by city, View details of the salon, Notification function when there is a new appointment, cancel an appointment

Gourmet Market Thailand 7

Building a sales website, Manage orders, Order function, Order management, product review, Order payment by visa/mastercard

XO Sections **尽**

XO Sections is a great solution with tons of customizing options

XHotel [↗]

Management and booking hotel

Hillridge 7

Agricultural construction insurance

Maby Salon [↗]

Book an appointment, Manage an appointment, View details of the salon, Notification function when there is a new appointment, cancel an appointment

Summoners Arena 7

Building a website to buy and sell heroes with tokens, Exchange tokens, Create and manage events

Open Source Software

Convert svg to icon

★ 6

Quillis Resize Image 🖸 🗷

A module resize image for quilljs

★ 15

React Sticky O 7

A library sticky element for reactjs

★7

More Projects...

CSS To Tailwindcss 🖸 🗷

Convert css to tailwindcss

★ 11

CSV Parser (7) 7

A module parse csv file for nodejs

***** 8

React OTP Input 🗘 🗷

A library otp input for reactjs

★ 12

Stacks

Frontend HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, Reactjs, Nextjs, Svelte, Vuejs, Vite, Rspack, Webpack

Backend Nodejs, Nestjs, MongoDB, PostgreSQL

DevOps Firebase, Nginx, Docker, Github Action, CI/CD

Languages C/C++

Education

Electronics Telecommunication Engineering, Engineer, Hanoi university of science and technology

Sep 2015 - Sep 2020

Interests

Reading

Coding

References

Nguyen Manh Thang

CEO at Agiletech Vietnam

Nguyen Hoai Nam

Techlead at Agiletech Vietnam

Neo Khuat

CTO at Beau Agency Vietnam



Vietnamese (Native speaker), English (Beginner)

Online Version

Last updated at July 17th 2024, 10:04:10 am